(Howard:)So I took it down to this buddy of mine
who deals with...
(Howard:)...shall we say, the seedy underbelly
of the collectibles world.
(Leonard:)Seedy underbelly?
Uh, your black-market phasers...
(Howard:)...your screen-worn Lieutenant Uhura
panties, that kind of stuff.
[HOWARD CLEARS THROAT]
(Raj:)Who's this mysterious buddy
you suddenly have?
(Howard:)Just a guy. I know a guy.
(Raj:)-Is it Eddie Crispo?
-No, I can't tell you who it is.
(Raj:)-Who else could it be? It has to be.
-I know lots of dangerous people.
(Raj:)-Name one.
-Eddie Crispo.
(Howard:)Anyway, he said this isn't a replica.
(Howard:)It's the real deal.
(Sheldon:)If you're suggesting that
that is the actual ring of power...
(Sheldon:)...forged by Sauron in Mount Doom...
(Sheldon:)...I look at you with an expression
of exhaustion...
...and ever-so-slight amusement.
[SCOFFS]
(Leonard:)He's not saying it's a magic ring.
(Leonard:)You're not, are you?
(Howard:)No, but it's close.
(Howard:)Look at the markings inside.
(Howard:)Those are production markings.